A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 4, Accession 4 FA1186
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges from China, 4
  - Civil Engineering and Architectural Education Study Team - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1981 February 18-March 12 (Box 53, Folder 523)
  - Civil Engineering and Architectural Education Study Team - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1981 February 18-March 12; FA1186:033 (Box 61)
    2 group photos of delegation in Washington, DC; enclosed in Wang Dashi to Julie Reinganum, August 19. 1981.
  - Stagecraft Study Team - General, 1981 July 8-30 (Box 54, Folder 524)
  - Stagecraft Study Team - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1981 July 8-30 (Box 54, Folder 525)
  - Stagecraft Study Team - Visits, 1981 July 8-30 (Box 54, Folder 526)
  - Education Research Delegation - General, 1981 September 17-October 8 (Box 54, Folder 527)
  - Education Research Delegation - Visits, 1981 September 17-October 8 (Box 54, Folder 528-529)
  - Education Research Delegation - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1981 September 17-October 8 (Box 54, Folder 530)
  - Film Delegation - General, 1981 October 14-November 7 (Box 54, Folder 531)
  - Film Delegation - General, 1981 October 14-November 7; FA1186:034 (Box 61)
    Snapshot of luncheon at Shih Chung-wen's house, October 1981. Enclosed in 1982 New Year's card to Julie Reinganum.
  - Film Delegation - Literature and Clippings, 1981 October 14-November 7 (Box 54, Folder 532)
  - Film Delegation - Thank Yous, 1981 October 14-November 7 (Box 55, Folder 533)
  - Chinese People's Political Consultative Conference Delegation - General, 1981 October 28-November 12 (Box 55, Folder 534)
  - Chinese People's Political Consultative Conference Delegation - Visits, 1981 October 28-November 12 (Box 55, Folder 535)
  - Chinese People's Political Consultative Conference Delegation - Hotel and Travel Arrangements, 1981 October 28-November 12 (Box 55, Folder 536)
  - Chinese People's Political Consultative Conference Delegation - Thank You Letters and Follow-Up, 1981 October 28-November 12 (Box 55, Folder 537)
  - Urban Design Study Team - General, 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 55, Folder 538)
  - Urban Design Study Team - Background and Planning, 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 55, Folder 539)
  - Urban Design Study Team - Visits (Racine), 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 55, Folder 540)
    Sino American Conference on Urban Design and Development Technology, Wingspread, October 29-31.
  - Urban Design Study Team - Visits (Chicago), 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 55, Folder 541)
    File consists of literature only; no correspondence.
  - Urban Design Study Team - Visits (Minneapolis), 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 55, Folder 542)
    File includes program book from Sino-American Conference on Urban Design and Development Technology, November 6-10, 1981.
  - Urban Design Study Team - Visits (Denver and San Francisco), 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 56, Folder 543)
  - Urban Design Study Team - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1981 October 28- November 21 (Box 56, Folder 544)
  - Urban Design Study Team - Report, Thank Yous, and Follow-Up, 1981 October 28- November 21; FA1186:035 (Box 61)
    9 color prints, including group photo of delegation, and additional negatives.
  - Writers Delegation, 1982 September 18-October 18 (Box 56, Folder 545)
- Conferences, Seminars, Workshops, and Dialogues, 5
  The Conferences, Seminars, Workshops, and Dialogues series documents some of the National Committee's early initiatives to increase public knowledge and understanding of China. From 1967 to 1971, the NCUSCR sponsored seminars and other programs for Regional Journalists around the U.S., with an aim of improving awareness and coverage of China in the press. It also reached out to local civic and business Community Leaders for membership and support for its seminars and presentations. In 1968, the NCUSCR engaged the Norwegian journalist Harald Munthe-Kaas to travel throughout the U. S. and speak about his experiences in China. In the early to mid- 1970s, the NCUSCR, with support from the Johnson Foundation, also organized a series of round tables and conferences to explore developing relations with China and the prospects for exchanges.
  - China and the Press Symposium - General, 1971 October 18 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - China and the Press Symposium - Press Packet, 1971 October 18 (Box 18, Folder 144)
  - China and the Press Symposium - Transcripts, 1971 October 18 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - China and the Press Symposium - Transcripts, 1971 October 18; FA1186:037; AV: Reel to Reel tape. (Box 61)
    Norman Webster, "Problems and Opportunities in Reporting about China," luncheon address, 1971 October 18.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copy currently unavailable.
  - Roundtable Meeting, Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 19, Folder 146-147)
  - Regional Journalists - Atlanta Seminar for Southern Journalists, 1968 February 29-March 2 (Box 19, Folder 148)
  - Regional Journalists - Denver Seminar for Journalists, 1970 April 10-11 (Box 19, Folder 149)
  - Regional Journalists - Denver Seminar on China, 1968 January 23 (Box 19, Folder 150)
  - Regional Journalists - Stanford University Seminar for Journalists, 1967 June 26-30 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Regional Journalists - Harald Munthe-Kaas Tour, 1968 January (Box 19, Folder 152)
    Meeting with Washington, DC, Journalists, January 31.
  - Regional Journalists - Colin McCullough Journalists Briefing (Washington, DC), 1970 March 3 (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Regional Journalists - Washington, DC, Journalists (Namelists), 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Regional Journalists - Seminar for Western Journalists (Proposed), 1969 (proposed) (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - Regional Journalists - Michigan Press Institute and Scholar Symposium, 1968 March (Box 20, Folder 156)
  - Regional Journalists - Harvard University Journalists' Seminar, 1967 July 13-15 (Box 20, Folder 157)
  - Regional Journalists - Harvard University Journalists' Seminar (Proceedings, Volume 1), 1967 July 13-15 (Box 20, Folder 158)
  - Regional Journalists - Harvard University Journalists' Seminar (Proceedings, Volume 2), 1967 July 13-15 (Box 20, Folder 159)
  - Regional Journalists - Harvard University Press-Study Seminars - General, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 160)
  - Regional Journalists - Harvard University Press-Study Seminars - Journalist's Guide to China, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 161)
  - Regional Journalists - Press - General Contacts and Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 162)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Chen, Jack, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 163)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Egashira, Kazuma, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 164)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - FitzGerald, C. P., 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 165)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - FitzGerald, Stephen, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Gayn, Mark, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 167)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - James, Francis, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 168)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Munthe-Kaas, Harald, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 169)
    Nowegian journalist Munthe-Kaas traveled throughout the U. S. in early 1968 as the guest of the NCUSCR, meeting with Community Leaders and speaking about China.
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Munthe-Kaas, Harald, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 170)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Oldham, C. H. G., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 171)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Wang Sheng and Cheng Hsueh-Chia, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 172)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Whitfield, Elsie, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 173)
  - Community Leaders (Names) - Wilson, Dick, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 174)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Atlanta 1 (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 10 (Box 21, Folder 175)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Atlanta 2, 1968 March (Box 21, Folder 176)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Baltimore (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 (Box 21, Folder 177)
    Munthe-Kaas event, February 13.
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Birmingham (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 10 (Box 21, Folder 178)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Boston, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 179)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Chicago (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 26 (Box 21, Folder 180)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Cincinnati, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 181)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Columbia, SC, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 182)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Columbus, OH, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Dallas, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 184)
    Munthe-Kaas event, January 15, 1968.
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Denver (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 23 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Detroit (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 29 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Houston, 1968 January and March (Box 22, Folder 187)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Indianapolis (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 February 6 (Box 22, Folder 188)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Los Angeles (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 19 (Box 22, Folder 189)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Louisville, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 190)
    Muthe-Kaas event, February 2, 1968; Richard Solomon, March 13, 1968.
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Miami, Tampa, St. Petersburg, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 191)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Minneapolis and St. Paul (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 25 (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Philadelphia, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    Munthe-Kaas event, February 14, 1968.
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Pittsburgh (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 April 4 (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - St. Louis (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 24 (Box 22, Folder 195)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Salt Lake City (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 18 (Box 22, Folder 196)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - San Francisco (Meetings and Contacts), 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 197)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - San Francisco (Roger Hilsman, Dick Wilson), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 198)
    Roger Hilsman Luncheon, March 6, 1967; Dick Wilson event, October 19, 1967.
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - San Francisco (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 17 (Box 22, Folder 199)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Seattle (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 January 22 (Box 22, Folder 200)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Washington, DC, Community Leaders (Dick Wilson), 1967 November 17 (Box 22, Folder 201)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Washington, DC, Community Leaders (Munthe-Kaas), 1968 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 202)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Wichita, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 203)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Wilmington, DE, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 204)
  - Community Leaders (Seminars and Contacts) - Winston-Salem, 1968 April 5 (Box 22, Folder 205)
  - University of Connecticut Symposium on the Chinese Communist Movement, 1971 March 25-27 (Box 22, Folder 206)
    Program schedule.
  - Conference on Sino-American Exchanges (Seattle), 1976 November 19 (Box 25, Folder 239)
    China and America: How We See Each Other after Five Years.
  - Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China - Correspondence and Planning, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 56, Folder 546-547)
    Roundtable meeting.
  - Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China - Background Material, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 56, Folder 548)
  - Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China - Program and Presentations, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 56, Folder 549)
  - Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China - Press Coverage, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 56, Folder 550)
  - Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China - Report, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 56, Folder 551)
  - Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China - Report, 1971 January 22-23 (Box 57, Folder 552)
  - Developing Exchanges with China, Roundtable Discussion, 1971 July 15 (Box 57, Folder 553)
    Folder labeled, "Coordinating Meeting."
  - Prospects and Problems of Exchanges with China, Roundtable Discussion, 1972 April 27 (Box 57, Folder 554-555)
  - Exchanges with the People's Republic of China, Roundtable Discussion, 1972 September 19-20 (Box 57, Folder 556-557)
    Wingspread meeting.
  - Exchanges with the People's Republic of China, Roundtable Meeting, 1973 March 1 (Box 57, Folder 558)
    Prospects for Exchanges with China: A Roundtable Discussion. NCUSCR, New York.
  - Wingspread Conferences - Conversations from Wingspread pertinent to the NCUSCR, Undated, circa 1974-1977? (Box 57, Folder 559)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Workshops (General Proposals), 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 560)
    For programs in Science and Medicine especially.
  - Wingspread Conferences - Possible Participants for Medical and Scientific Workshops, 1969-1972 (Box 57, Folder 561)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Proposed Conference, Assessing the China Visit, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 562)
  - Wingspread Conferences - China in the Schools - Program, Invitations, and Papers, 1972 June 6-8 (Box 58, Folder 563)
  - Wingspread Conferences - China in the Schools - Correspondence, 1972 June 6-8 (Box 58, Folder 564)
  - Wingspread Conferences - China in the Schools - Conference Report, 1972 June 6-8 (Box 58, Folder 565)
    China in the Schools: Directions and Priorities.
  - Wingspread Conferences - Education in the People's Republic of China - General, 1973 April 27-29 (Box 58, Folder 566)
    Includes Program and Report.
  - Wingspread Conferences - Education in the People's Republic of China - Correspondence, 1973 April 27-29 (Box 58, Folder 567-568)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Education in the People's Republic of China - Planning, 1973 April 27-29 (Box 58, Folder 569)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Science in China - General, 1973 May 29-31 (Box 58, Folder 570)
    Includes Program and Report
  - Wingspread Conferences - Science in China - Correspondence and Planning, 1973 May 29-31 (Box 58, Folder 571)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Science in China - Background Readings, 1973 May 29-31 (Box 59, Folder 572)
    Folder labeled, "Peggy's File" (Peggy Blumenthal).
  - Wingspread Conferences - Health Care in China - Correspondence, Planning, and Report, 1973 November 28-30 (Box 59, Folder 573)
    Still Image - Color slide with group portrait of Health Care in China conference participants at Wingspread.
  - Wingspread Conferences - Health Care in China - Correspondence, Planning, and Report, 1973 November 28-30; FA1186:036 (Box 61)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Health Care in China - Correspondence, Planning, and Report, 1973 November 28-30 (Box 59, Folder 573)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Health Care in China - Background and Prior Proposals, 1973 November 28-30 (Box 59, Folder 574)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations - General, 1974 May 6-7 (Box 59, Folder 575)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations - Correspondence, 1974 May 6-7 (Box 59, Folder 576)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations - Planning and Background, 1974 May 6-7 (Box 59, Folder 577)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Women in China, American Perspectives, 1974 June 25 (Box 59, Folder 578)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Women in China, American Perspectives, 1974 June 25 (Box 60, Folder 579)
  - Wingspread Conferences - University Outreach Programs on East Asia - Correspondence, Planning, and Background, 1975 September 28-29 (Box 60, Folder 580-582)
    University Outreach Programs on East Asia: Linkages with School and Community.
  - Wingspread Conferences - University Outreach Programs on East Asia - Background Readings, 1975 September 28-29 (Box 60, Folder 583)
  - Wingspread Conferences - University Outreach Programs on East Asia - Report, 1975 September 28-29 (Box 60, Folder 584)
  - Wingspread Conferences - Exchange Experience with China - The Past, Present and Future, 1977 February 20-21 (Box 60, Folder 585)
- Art and Archaeology, 7
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 217-218)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 219)
    Includes copy of grant proposal to the NEH for funding of travel grants and educational programs.
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Australian Tour, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 220)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Clippings and Press Releases, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 221)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Clippings and Press Releases, 1972-1974; FA1186:010 (Box 61)
    8x10 black and white transparency of 3 statues of soldiers on horseback.
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Education Efforts, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 222)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Education Program Meeting, 1974 August 12 (Box 24, Folder 223)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Grant-in-Aid Applicants, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 224)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Grant-in-Aid Recipients, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 225)
    Includes material on second-round selection.
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Grant-in-Aid Selection Panel, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 226)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Interest from Other Museums, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 227)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Interest from Other Museums, 1973-1974; FA1186:011 (Box 61)
    3 8x10 black and white photos of Dallas Museum of Fine Arts exhibit spaces.
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Mailings and Announcements, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 228)
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Mailings and Announcements, 1974-1975; FA1186:039 (Box 62)
    Oversize: 11x17 poster of talk by Shirley Sun, UC-Santa Cruz, June 26, 1975.
  - Archaeological Exhibit - Paris, London, Vienna, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 229)
  - Archaeology Education Programs, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    Louisville, KY; Peoria, IL; Los Angeles; San Francisco.
  - Archaeology Slide Show - Correspondence and Distribution, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - Archaeology Slide Show - Correspondence and Distribution, 1975-1977; FA1186:012; 9 Color slides (in 2 sets) (Box 61)
    2 slides of Pan Po site exhibits (sent by R. Poore); 7 slides of artifacts from The Chinese Exhibition, Royal Ontario Museum, Toronto.
  - Archaeology Slide Show - Narration Script, circa 1975 (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - Archaeology Slide Show - Narration (Slides), circa 1975; FA1186:013 (Box 61)
    32 color slides, numbered and captioned, "Art and Archaeology in China."
  - Archaeology Slide Show - Narration (Recording), circa 1975; FA1186:038 (Box 61)
    AV: cassettte tape (Art and Archaeology in China narration, 25:10)
  - Asian Art Museum of San Francisco - Archaeological Exhibit, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - KQED Documentary (Six Hundred Millennia - China's History Unearthed), 1975 (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Archaeological Exhibit, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - National Gallery of Art (Washington, DC) - Archaeological Exhibit, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 236)
    Includes 2 sets of postcard images of artifacts in the exhibit.
  - Nelson Gallery - Atkins Museum (Kansas City) - Archaeological Exhibit, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 237)
    The Art and Archaeology series contains files relating to the exhibit, Archaeological Finds of the People's Republic of China, which toured the U. S. in 1974-1975, opening at the National Gallery of Art in Washington, DC, and then traveling to the Nelson Gallery – Atkins Museum in Kansas City, MO, and the Asian Art Museum of San Francisco.
  - Times Atlas of China Offer, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 238)
- Programs, Projects, and Proposals, 8
  The Programs, Projects, and Proposals series contains files relating to the NCUSCR's Media Services program, 1971-1977, and to its Education projects – especially the Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP), 1973-1975, and the Project on Asian Studies in Education (PASE), 1971-1975.
  The Media Services program helped organize news briefings on China and provided bibliographies and background readings for journalists and others engaging in early exchange programs – particularly for President Nixon's trip to China in 1972. The Media Services files consist primarily of memos and correspondence by Donald W. Klein, a political scientist who was hired in 1971 as program consultant for mass media.
  The National Committee's educational programs gathered information on university-based resources and programs in Asian Studies and encouraged links with primary and secondary school educators through teacher workshops and the development of instructional and resource materials. The Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) developed training programs and resources for teachers on Chinese culture and U.S.–China relations. The Project on Asian Studies in Education (PASE), based at the University of Michigan, formed a resource center and provided similar outreach and training for high-school and college teachers and graduate students.
  - Media Services - General, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 240)
  - Media Services - Assistance to Publishers and Press, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 241)
  - Media Services - Intellectual Digest, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 242)
  - Media Services - Washington Post and L.A. Times Series, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 243)
  - Media Services - Assistance to Radio and Television, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 244)
  - Media Services - Nixon Visit to China, 1972 February (Box 25, Folder 245)
    Includes Journalists' Briefing, February 9-11. Includes pocket-calendar card with photographic image of "woman country doctor."
  - Media Services - Arcata Microfilm, Inc., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 246)
  - Media Services - Media Seminars, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 247)
  - Media Services - Journalist Panel at the American Society of Newspaper Editors (ASNE) Convention, 1974 April (Box 26, Folder 248)
  - Media Services - Briefings for Press Accompanying President Ford to China, 1975 November 13-14 (Box 26, Folder 249)
  - Media Services - Press Briefing for Cyrus Vance Visit to China, 1977 August 18 (Box 26, Folder 250)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Correspondence, 1973-1975 February (Box 26, Folder 251-255)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Correspondence, 1973 June-October; FA1186:014; 10 snapshots from BAYCEP programs (Box 61)
    Photos enclosed in Margo Rosen to Peggy Blumenthal, 1974 October 24.
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Correspondence, 1975 January-February; FA1186:015; 5 color slides. (Box 61)
    Numbered slides accompany the Filial Piety Exercise (BAYCEP); file includes exercise and description
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Correspondence, 1975 March-December (Box 27, Folder 256)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - History and Background, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 257-258)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Grant Proposal, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 259)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Proposal and Survey Administration, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 260)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Phase 1 Report, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 261)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Dominican College China Symposium, Evaluations, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 262)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Literature, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 263)
  - Bay Area China Education Project (BAYCEP) - Norton Simon Foundation Proposal, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 264)
  - Project on Asian Studies in Education (PASE) - General, 1971-1973, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 265-266)